Guide to the Richard White papers SC1323
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Richard White papers
circa 1670-2006, bulk 1980s-2006
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
White, Richard, 1947-
SC1323
60 Linear Feet (40 boxes)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Richard White, 2017.
Scope and Contents
Collection includes professional files, teaching materials, files related to books and other articles, and audiovisual materials.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical / Historical
Richard White is an historian of the United States specializing in the American West, the history of capitalism, environmental history, history and memory, and Native American history. His work has occasionally spilled over into Mexico, Canada, France, Australia and Ireland. He is a MacArthur Fellow and a recipient of the Mellon Distinguished Professor Award. His work has won numerous academic prizes, and he has twice been a finalist for the Pulitzer Prize. Source: http://history.stanford.edu/people/richard-white
American history; History -- Study and teaching.; White, Richard, 1947-; White, Richard, 1947-; White, Richard, 1947-; Stanford University. Department of History.
- Professional
  - Laws and Treaties, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Impact conference folder, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - National Archives Publications (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NARA (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Jessica Terseh, 1998 Apr (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ex 33 Puset shellfish case, 1824-1881 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Shellfish, 1869 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Xerox for lawyers, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - White (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Xerox - for Fobert, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Fortune - Electric, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Willis Batcheller (includes later corr. U.S./Canada) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Land Management Unit 11 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Land Planning Reports, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The Huntington correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Weber letters Survey - pt. 34, 1911-1914 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers - unsertes, 1850 - 1861 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - LMU 18, 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Xeroe - lawyers, 1886 Feb 5 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - notebook (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - MacArthur, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Western Historical Quarterly, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cutter - ue - Lilo, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Kelsey: Amherst Plan, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Anthro - Kinship - Triby (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Wallace - Weise (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Quesic Murders, 1250s (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Thomson Enquiry (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - of P (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - index cards (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - History Reports: E. J. Brooks (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Discussion - New Treaties R407-H08, 1860s (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - CIA, 1850s (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Missionary reports - pre, 1861 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Vogel Article (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Withdrawal of Lands, 1850s (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Further Research (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - CIA, 1850-1860s (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Ottawas, 1900-1910 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Social Condition - MI, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Laws (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Board of Indian Commissioners Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chiefs G.T., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Ed. G.T. (+ Genl. Services), 1960-1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Drafts - Chapter 1-3 G.T. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - G.T., 1860's (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Ca: Rns on Churchill as historian, 1855-1930 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports CIA, 1870s (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - G.T., 1870's (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Patents under Treaty, 1871-1876 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Indian Homesteads Investigations Frauds (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Patents under Treaty, 1860-1870 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Land Fraud Specific Cases- L.T., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - New Indian History education (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - R409, 1870-1871 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - RL/08, 1868-1869 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sault St. Marie Land exempt from taxation, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Sugar Island: comm building, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - SSM draft (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - SSM interviews (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - SSM native economy, 1855 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sault Ste. Marie Bands; native forms of government nature of tribes etc. (secondary materials) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Reel 413 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - SSM - govt. relations general R407-408, 1860 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Recognition of band chiefs after 1855 -- Sault St. Marie (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - R414, 1879 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - R415, 1880 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - R412, 1877 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Amer-Canadian problem SSU, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Meekel Report, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Sugar Island - Bay Mills Relations, 1938-1960 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - R. Procedure (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Richard White Mail (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Bands -- Durant Roll (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Sugar Island - General, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Sugar Island: Termination, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Sugar Island: Land Acquisition, BIA File, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Duplicate Exams, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Durant Rolls (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Early memory (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Sault St. Marie Termination and Citizenship Direct References (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Sugar Island: Lands, Transfer, Org. of Sugar Island Corporation, 1950s (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - US v State of Michigan Supplementary Report, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Sault St. Marie Land held in trust (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Federal payments to bands after expiration of annuities (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - SSM Claims, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Exec. Doc., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Creation of Parliamentary B. (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Commons for C. (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Drafts of Final Report = Sault Ste. Marie (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Sault Ste. Marie Government Correspondence, 1900-1920 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Sault Ste. Marie, 1920s (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - R411 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - SSM Sources (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - History 301A - Workbook Materials (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Allocation Loss of Treaty Lands SSM (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - A - S. Law B. (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Sault Ste. Marie, 1890s (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Patents (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Trust Land - Permanent Reservation, etc., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Land-Patents SSM (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Durant Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Sault Ste. Marie, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - SSM Org., 1960s (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Sugar Island: Comm. Building, Trust Status, Enrollment of SSM band, 1950s (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Chapt. 3 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Sault St. Marie Government Schools after 1889 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Early Caperions, 1855-1950 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Tanner reports on Sault St. Mary (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - SSM - government Relations R405-406, 1855-1861 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - R410, 1872-1873 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Rump Parliament R406, 1858-1861 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - R404, 1883-1885 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Genl. Cono. SSM, 1860s (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Daily Life, 1870s (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - SSM General conditions, 1855 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Village sites, pop. Movement before 1855 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Johnson, David N. "Free Accompaniments for Manuals" Book II useful documents, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Bay Mills minutes, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - SSM: Tribal Archives, 1950-1960 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Fowler Report, 1991 May (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Fisheries Conf. Feb., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Missouri Hst. Society, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Montana Talk, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - UCLA: Valerie + Georges conf. papers, 1954-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - WHA-96, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Inst. NA West, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Illustrations text (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cambridge picture, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Picture reciepts RW costs, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Jim McClurken, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Claire Martin, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - R. White (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mark Fiese, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Rollings - Rec. etc, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Gregory Smoak, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Keith Widder, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Buffalo Bill/Turner (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Notes on sources etc. Newberry, 1843 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Turner Exhibit - pos. sources, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Buffalo Bill: programs, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Wilderness conference Welser state, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Nat. standards (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Warren center talk, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Schechter, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - National Faculty, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - National Faculty Seattle, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Ethnohistory Board of Editors, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Ethnohistory (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - WHA Award of Merit (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Ballantinos, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Mellana, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Huntington - Shammas paper (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Pennsylvania, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Mountain West - Turner, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Early American History, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Society of Colonial, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Insignia films, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Oregon Trail, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Reed talk, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Text reviews, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Letter to Richard (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Speech Forum (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Buffalo Bill Center, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Manuscript Reviews (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Salish, 1842 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - US vs. Michigans: Fishing Rights, 1890 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Pacific Northwest Indian Fisheries Commission, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Fishing Stats, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - State - tribal planning (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Fishing Rights Pollution, 1973-1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Fishing Regs., 1972-1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Trap- Net selectivity - DNR Report, 1980 Mar (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Michigan Water Quality and Pollution, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Liston and Williamson Lake Whitefish… Whitefish Bay, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Indians - Materials on Current Issues (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Fishery + Wildlife Research, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Fisheries Studies, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - See MI fisheries Div., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Tribal Testimony, 1980 Feb (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Bay Mills Interviews, 1980 Jun (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Ad Hoc Working Goup Report Tribal Fisheries -- Lake Superior, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Sportsfishermen Groups on Indian Fishing, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Charges/Indian Fishing (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Dingell Bill, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Notes/ cross clipping files, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Environmental History Review Article, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Georges Borchardt, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Organic Machine Partial Draft (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Mozart Street (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Ahanagran draft, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Ahanagran w/ my mother's changes, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Mom book, Draft remembering Ahanagran (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - History 122 questions evaluating prosecution's case, 1978 Fall (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - JJ draft, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Toronto - misc papers, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Nebraska, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Additional articles, 1975-1983 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Can. Arch. Meetings - misc., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Outlaw paper (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Western Outlaws and social bandits, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Notes - Dalton and Doolin; James Gage - Social Bandit Paper, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Outlaws San Francisco paper, 1980 Spring (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Doolin gang, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Supporters of Jesse James (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Barnard - group protection - anti-vigilante (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Daltons - descrption of crime, 1892-1893 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Vigilance committees Oklahoma, 1893 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Deputy Marshalls - Attitude, toward, etc., 1894 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - E. Dalton - "Beyond the Law (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Stillwater Eagle Gazette (misc.), 1895 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Clay, 1870 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - First hand material on gang member, 1892-1893 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Census Material - Missouri Jesse James, 1790-1890 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Other Crimes - Oklahoma, 1891-1894 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Grassroots socialism Green (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - JJ, 1880 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Dalton - Doolin - Payne Co. Pops, 1894 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Attributes of Outlaw (cultural), 1889 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Payne County - general, politics, etc, 1891 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Dalton - Doolin supporters, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Dalton gang - newspapers (populist), 1894 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Local attitudes - Oklahoma, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - JJ stories + songs (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Terrill, 1892-1893 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Cracker weck (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Guerillas (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Hobsbawn Social Outlaw paper notes and references, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Gang as modern, 1897 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - NYE - crime in modern societies, 1894 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Puldie Land laws + culturals, 1883 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - JJ, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Misc. bandit/outlaw material (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Indian territory - outlaws (new), 1937 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Outlaw paper San Francisco misc., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Random notes - ute water (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Ute Water, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - "Story of Cole Younger", 1955 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Colonial Imperial, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Gilroy Black Atlantic, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Inga Clendinnen: "Fierce and Unnatural Cruelty", 1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Gutierrez - Berdaches (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Hackel: Missions, 1979-1830 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Phys Isaac Articles, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Historians + Indians, 1989 Jan (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Leplore: King Phillip, 1994 Oct 15 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Natalie Davis: Iroquois Women, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Gordon Wood Radical+ Amer. Rev. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Hadlock political social org. Northeastern Indians (articles) (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Faragher - Daniel Boone, 1990 Jun (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Alan Taylor - Rev. Frontier (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Lemon - Mentalite (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - McCay Last of the Fathers, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Lockridge Land, Population and the Evolution of New England Society, 1630-1790 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Forrest McDonald - Ethnic Origins of the American People (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Anne Norton: Alternative Americas (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Rose: Reforming Women, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Carol Shammes How Self-Sufficient Wes Early America (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Daniel Snydacker - Kinship and Community in Rural Penn, 1749-1820 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Booknets Wilentz (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Women Reform (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Whittenburg - North Carolina Reg. (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Jefferson (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Henretta - Social Mobility (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Families and Farms Henretta (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Henretta: Families + Farms - Mentalite (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Jordan: Familial Politics - Killing of King, 1776 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Johnson: Mayo Greenleaf, 1766-1818 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Ekirch, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Appleby, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Breen Back to Sweat (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Readings- Genl. Lecture (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Norma Baseh. Women, Legal History, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Readings for Graduate seminar, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Berquist: Imperialism (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Bissel - One Generation to Another: mobility 10th century, Windsor (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Christopher Clark (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Clark - Household Economy, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Donald Duck, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Countryman, Revele., 1994 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Demos American Family in Past Time, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Sally Deutsch: Learning to Talk more like a man, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - David Galensen Middling People or Common Sort (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Paula Giddings, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Jaclyn David Hall sexual violence (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Paul Johson Strange Cargo (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Indian History Best notes + summary (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Misc. book notes 464 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Indians (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Problem of Tribes as category (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Parman - Navajo + New Deal (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Bodes Indian History notes, 1966-1977 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - White - W Indiana - reading notes (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Peckham Pontiac (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Tanner - Captivity (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Cadillac Memoir (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Lahontan (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Colin Calloway - Indians, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Jaenen "Sauvage", 1982 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - European Impact, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Metcalf - Who Should Rate (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Merrell: Montour (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Richter: War + Culture - Iroq. Experience, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - Metis Article, 1823 (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - Wallace - Revitalization (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - 20 cent. Indian nooknotes + late 19th, 1905-1906 (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - Spring/West conference (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - Marnis Epilogue (Box 29, Folder 70)
  - Digital - Va (Box 29, Folder 71)
  - Merced (Box 29, Folder 72)
  - Stanford - Canter Lecture (Box 29, Folder 73)
  - Sally Deutsh Promotion (Box 29, Folder 74)
  - Sun Valley, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 75)
  - Can. U.S. Fishing (Box 29, Folder 76)
  - Joyce Chaplin, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 77)
  - Y2K, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 78)
  - Indian Demography (Box 29, Folder 79)
  - Depopulation, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 80)
  - Population (Box 29, Folder 81)
  - Virginia Anderson paper, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 82)
  - Navajo Attitude toward nature ceremonials (Box 29, Folder 83)
  - Carlos - Lewis Indians + Beaver, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 84)
  - Notes and Documents (Box 29, Folder 85)
  - A. Crosby Virgin Soil Epidemics WMQ, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 86)
  - Columbian Consequences (Box 29, Folder 87)
  - Day- Indian as Erol. Factor (Box 29, Folder 88)
  - Flores: Bisen, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 89)
  - De Mallie - Lakota G.D. (Box 29, Folder 90)
  - Hst. 822 Gordon Day the Indian as An Ecological Factor in the N.E. Forest (Box 29, Folder 91)
  - Hickerson Virginia Deer (Box 29, Folder 92)
  - Why the great plans are treeless (Box 29, Folder 93)
  - Luckert nav. Hunting Tradition (Box 29, Folder 94)
  - Kunstadler: So. Athabaskan Herding patterns, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 95)
  - Briet - Sierra Club Indian - religion, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 96)
  - Birth of peace pipe (Box 29, Folder 97)
  - Lumbee/Mashbee (Box 29, Folder 98)
  - Final class (Box 29, Folder 99)
  - Sollors - Last class (Box 29, Folder 100)
  - Hst 498 week 2 Indian, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 101)
  - Hst 498 first readings (Box 29, Folder 102)
  - Sollors (Box 29, Folder 103)
  - Sollors 91 (Box 29, Folder 104)
  - Berkhofer (Box 29, Folder 105)
  - Fouler - shared symbols, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 106)
  - Eastman (Box 29, Folder 107)
- Teaching
  - Inventing Indians, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Deloria Indian Sov. N.A. Experience (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Indian Experience Reservations (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Experience E. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Western Indians (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Indian Experience week 3 Deloria Body (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Dependency (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Intro-Indians in Larger Society Code Talkers (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - "Indian" Identity (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - End of Termination (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - New Deal Indian Ed. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - NA. Experience - Resource Materials (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Placement Program (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Indian Education, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - NCAI, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Hist. 465 Post WWII (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Hist. 465 Econ Dev. On Res. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Indians and Corporation (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - AIM (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Native American Experience Silko - Ceremony (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Hist. 463 Jennings N.E. - P. War (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Hist. 463 Jennings - # 10 N.E. - Metacom (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Hist. 463 Slave Wars # 7 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Hist. 463 So. Playoff #13 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Hist. 469 Conflict (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Hst. 463 Fr. Indian War decline of Irog. Hegemony (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Irog. Haven Del Shawner Fox # 14 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Cultural Change - Neolin Hist. 463 # 17 Pontias Rebellion (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Cultural Crisis + Amer. Rev. # 18 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - The Prophet Hist. 463 Speech + Black Hawk (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Eastern Indians and IRA (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Hist. 463 Handsome Lake (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Hist. 463 So. Nations (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Hist. 463 Tecumseh (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - West Coast Wars (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Hist. 463 Decline of Subsistence + Dependency (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Hist. 463 Confederations (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Spicer Early Res System + Conquest of Plains (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Trad and Exhange History 463 # 4 (Cronon + Jennings) (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Hist. 463 Black Hawk (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Spicer Early Res System + Conquest of Plains (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Seminds Hist. 463 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Hist. 464 Background, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Secular Pan. Indianism Hist. 465 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Holder (pt. 2) Nomads (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Hist. 464 Pueblos (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Pawnee Ghost Dance (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Ishi Western Res. Etc (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Hist. 463 # 12 Trade + Na. Playoff (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Athapascans History 464 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Hist. 463. # 11 Cultural Change - Axteil (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Response to Reservations (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Rebellions Against Reservation System (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Navajo - Long Walk Early Rs. (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Hst. 463 Removal (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Eastern Removal Intertribal Conflict (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Eastern Indians - Intro. Lecture 1 Hist. 463 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Hist. 463 # 8 or 9 Powhatten Opecancanough (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - History of the West: Lecture Economics of 17th and 18th Century settlement (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Lecture 9 Discarded Western History; Lecture Brit Policy after 1763 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Indians 20th Century (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Cherokee lecture materials (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Reading Packets Indian History (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Questions Indian Course 20th Centuy (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Pan-Indianism NAC (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Hist. 464 Acculturation - Mission (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Termination (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Relocation (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Termination H. (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Reformers + Education Hist. 465 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Cothers - Questions + Indian Awareness Week (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Indian Police / Judge (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Hist. 463 Tecamseh (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Fraud in Indian Country (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Winter in the Blood (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Coming into the Country (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Hist. 465 New Indian Policy Dependency (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Hist. 469 # 4 Modern D. Urban Indians (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - 469 #5 Legal Relation (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Hist. 469 # 6 Iroquois Wars Culture (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Hist. 406 Beaver Wars # 6 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Hist. 469 Sealpig War # 7 (use w/ Trade and North Playoff) (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Hist. 463 Imperial Wars Breakdown of Playoff #15 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Pawnee (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Gender (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Paternalism Cherokee (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Hist. 329 Nomadic Conquest (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Hist. 456 Black Elk 1 - 76 (Box 16, Folder 88)